Hello hello everyone today we are going to tell you about Max Bupa
rates and plain vs AC bonds with
sex, both were launched some time back
and nowadays there is a lot of demand in the market,
if you are looking for a home for yourself then subscribe and subscribe, there is no
entry limit in
subscribe and subscribe and subscribe,
no one else has free
hospitalization in Chhattisgarh, do subscribe by clicking on the subscribe button, you
can use your room according to your choice and
subscribe unlimited subscribe,
if you have some balance
left then you can use it,
if you talk about your Samir and subscribe set
then this is a very good feature
which is unlimited free subscribe,
subscribe, when the
screenshot is shown, you can subscribe in this, you can
subscribe to super no claim bonus,
which is to subscribe to the channel,
after this your 50% no claim bonus of
additional add is in this player which
will increase by 2%, AC teacher and if you
subscribe and talk about modern treatment
then subscribe subscribe  You
can subscribe for those who are
employed and for their family, you
can get the test done from Lips Holi, which I am
putting on the screen, you can check it, you can
subscribe for similar sewing, you can
subscribe and you
can subscribe for maximum,
whatever you do, for
example, if you have not subscribed for red color,
which is a very unique
feature, such a number will be available, if we
talk about treatment, then
in both the products, you have one treatment
subscription, mistreatment, it means that in
such a situation, if the policy holder is
employed in a war hospital, then at that time the
policy holder can subscribe to his home, in this,
aloe vera is required and in this, pre and post
hospitalization is not available, which
in both the products, treatment for 7 minutes means,
both the Ayurveda Siddha Unani
products, there are guidelines in this too, from
where you get the treatment done or there should be a government
hospital,
they need agreement guava center, if we
talk about organ donor, then in both the products,
you are covered for 7 minutes, in such a body,
whatever expenses you incur
for donor cover, that is your over and above 5 inches
and  For example, if you have an insurance claim of ₹10 lakh
and a donation claim of ₹5,000
comes in, then the ₹5 lakh will be
additional. Home health care is
covered by both companies.
You can get a second medical opinion in both products. You can
also take some additional supplements in your body, for example,
you can consult a doctor online or a
dietitian. You can also
avail the Balance Program at
Max Bupa.
You can get up to 30% discount on renewal if
you achieve their targets, which are
some of their fitness goals like
how many steps you have to account for,
which we are putting on the screen. You
can check these. Whereas in ICC,
you get some points. When you
add your hair status on their portal,
you can DM those points,
which can be very helpful in your OPD.
In Max Bupa, you can add an additional rider
called "Best Rider".
After that, you will not get any  You will not have to pay for non-perishable items
from your pocket.
Plus, if you have a claim of up to Rs 5,000,
you will not get a no-claim bonus and
inflation will be covered. While
this is what you subscribe to, you get benefits on channels
and these features must be added
because not only do you get a lot of
prepaid items, apart from this,
you can also set optional riders.
Like in ICC Lombard, you can
add dental benefit of Hospital Delhi. Similarly,
in Max Bupa, accidental benefit, critical
illness, all these are optional for you, which you
can add by paying an extra premium.
Talking about discounts,
if you pay 2 years
premium together with Max Bupa, then you get a
discount of 7.5 percent and if you pay 3 years
premium together, then
you get a discount of 50%, whereas if you
put the renewal on another renewal, then
you get an additional discount of 2.5 percent,
whereas on this Monday, the 2 year premium is paid on the same
pattern and the 3 year premium is paid.
There is a discount of 12.5% ​​on the policy rate of Naukri
Policy Medical
Kabir Saheb. There is
no pre-policy medical checkup in Max Bupa, whereas in ICC
people, if you support Alsi, then there is
no pre-policy medical checkup till childhood years and in Forest Policy,
if you enter after 65 years, then
you will have to give medical checkup. TPA is in-
house of both the companies and panel
hospital is in Max Bupa at around 700 panel
hospitals, whereas in ICC people, there are
around 5000 hospital channels. The
premium in Max Bupa is divided in two zones,
Delhi-NCR, Mumbai, Navi Mumbai,
Kolkata and Gujarat, whereas by turning
on the settings, Rest of India is in hatred. This does
not mean that you cannot get your treatment done in school,
that you can get your treatment done anywhere
without any limit, whereas in ICC
people, there is no zone division in the
entire country, the premium rate is same in the entire country. The
renewal is
life-long in both the products. Talking about family size,
you can add 200+ sides in Max Bupa,
whereas in this  You can subscribe to Loot,
waiting period both the products subscribe
one month cover subscribe appointed subscribe
appointed you can take subscription within 15 days
if you cancel within 15 days
which is your 261 side you can cancel it if it gets deleted then
this
is a very good product among both the products you should subscribe and
like both if you liked the video then
if you subscribe and
keep bringing videos then please
like and subscribe our channel thank you for
watching